http://www.axiontech.com/privacy.html

CART (
0 )
SUPPORT
CONTACT
FAQ
Email Address  New User?
Password  Forgot?
Components  |  Batteries1408 Vinylex Dr. Carrollton, TX 75006
ALL
Accessories  Cables & Adapters  Cameras  Cases  Cd / Dvd Burners  Cd/dvd Duplicators  Combo Deals  Controllers  Desktop Pcs  Digital Frames  Enclosure  Fans & Heatsinks  Firewire  Floppy Drive  Games Hardware  Gps / Navigation  Hard Drives  Keyboards, Mice  Media  Media Players  Memory & Usb Drives  Memory Modules  Monitors & Projectors  Motherboards  Networking  Networking - Wireless  Notebook  Others  Power Protection  Power Supplies  Printers, Scanners & Faxes  Processors  Projectors  Security & Surveillance  Sound Cards  Speakers & Headphones  Video Cards
CUSTOMER SERVICE
How To Order
Order Status & Tracking #
RMA Status
POPULAR BRANDS
AMD
ASUS
ATI
Privacy Statement
AxionTech.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Axiontech.com
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. This site contains links to other sites. AxionTech.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites.
Personal Information Security
At AxionTech.com, it is our primary concern to protect customer information and provide a safe and secure online ordering. Our online ordering, where we get all your personal information, is using the most advanced technology available, [Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and firewall technology], to keep your personal information secure from unauthorized access. Our sites uses an order form for customers to buy products, we collect your contact information (like name, address, email address, and phone number) and financial information (like credit card numbers), to process your order. This information will be kept confidential.
Credit Card Information
Your financial information is used for third-party banking to process your order. They are obligated to keep your personal information confidential.
Email Address
At AxionTech.com, your email address will be used to inform you about your shipping tracking number, order number, and the total purchase for your order. We do not give or sell this information to other companies. We only use this information for further contact with you about your order and to provide better customer service.
Name, Address, and Phone Number
Your name, address, and phone number then will be stored in our system so that we can better serve you when you return to our site or when you call us back.
All this information will be kept in a different server, which only the staff of AxionTech.com will have access.
Compliant
AxionTech.com's privacy policy has been reviewed and in full compliant of strict guidelines by the Better Business Bureau and DIGICERT.Click to VerifySSL Certificates
Computer Services
Dallas PC Repair Services
Dallas Metroplex Onsite Services
Computer Recycling Services
We service many brands of desktops
Best Price Guarantee
Customer Service
How To Order
Affiliates:
Houston Computer Store -
San Antonio Computer Store -
K12 Education Computer Systems
